But back to Renita...
and this email!
She at the computer, y'all.
She's stressed.
She wanna say...
"Why you not reading my shit?"
But she can't say that,
so you know what she has to say?
Delete, delete, delete, delete.
(SIGHS)
"Per my previous email..."
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
But there is a behavior
that white women
and women who happen to be white
(SCOFFS) are doing.
It's an infraction
that you're committing
on a regular basis
that all of us in here
would love for you
to stop doing.
It's plaguing offices
everywhere.
Please...
We beg of you...
Stop CC'ing
all these unnecessary people
-on these goddamn emails!
-(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
Stop!
Why you sharing
all these goddamn emails?
She ain't got shit to do
with what we doin' over here!